Guide to the R. Stuart Hummel Family Papers M1607
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series II. MILDRED STUART HUMMEL and WILLIAM F. HUMMEL PAPERS, 1890-1976
  - Subseries II: MILDRED STUART HUMMEL CORRESPONDENCE, circa 1890-1975
    - Flora Sheldon to Mildred Stuart Hummel, 1927-1929 (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Polly Small to Mildred Stuart Hummel, 1970 (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Alice Longden Smith to Mildred Stuart Hummel, 1899-1970 (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Frank M. and Bess Toothaker to Mildred Stuart Hummel, 1966-1968 (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Josie Trindle to Mildred Stuart Hummel, 1903-1905 (Box 132, Folder 11)
    - Mamie Wilson to Mildred Stuart Hummel, 1902-1905 (Box 132, Folder 12)
    - Daisy Youtz to Mildred Stuart Hummel, 1928-1967 (Box 132, Folder 13)
    - Mildred Stuart Hummel, miscellaneous incoming correspondence, 1895-1904 (Box 132, Folder 14)
    - Mildred Stuart Hummel, miscellaneous incoming correspondence, 1905-1906 (Box 132, Folder 15)
    - Mildred Stuart Hummel, miscellaneous incoming correspondence, 1907-1927 (Box 132, Folder 16)
    - Mildred Stuart Hummel, miscellaneous incoming correspondence, 1928-1934 (Box 132, Folder 17)
    - Mildred Stuart Hummel, miscellaneous incoming correspondence, 1935-1968 (Box 132, Folder 18)
  - Subseries III. WILLIAM F. HUMMEL PERSONAL MATERIALS and SUBJECT FILES
    - William F. Hummel, childhood, Warrenton (Mo.) and Nashville (Ill.) (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - William F. Hummel, childhood, Warrenton (Mo.) and Nashville (Ill.) (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - William F. Hummel, high school sketchbooks, circa 1903 (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - William F. Hummel, high school sketchbooks, circa 1903 (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - William F. Hummel, University of Chicago, Academy, circa 1904 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - William F. Hummel, University of Chicago, Academy, circa 1904 (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - William F. Hummel, University of Chicago, circa 1906-1908 (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - William F. Hummel, China years, 1908-1927 (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - William F. Hummel, China years, 1908-1927 (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - William F. Hummel, China years, 1908-1927 (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - William F. Hummel, Methodist Episcopal ordination certificates, (English and Chinese), 1917 (Flat-box 134, Folder 1)
    - William F. Hummel, University of Southern California, honor society certificate, circa 1931 (Flat-box 134, Folder 2)
    - William F. Hummel, University of Nanking, 1930-1952 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - William F. Hummel, University of Southern California, circa 1931 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - William F. Hummel, teaching career, 1931-1975 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - William F. Hummel, lecture tours to Asia, 1934-1936 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - William F. Hummel, lectures (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - William F. Hummel, lectures (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - William F. Hummel, lectures (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - William F. Hummel, published writings: includes a reprint of article published in Pacific Historical Review, December, 1935, "Ka’ang Yu Wei, Historical Critic and Social Philosopher, 1858-1927", circa 1930-1938 (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - William F. Hummel, library list (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - William F. Hummel and Kang Youwei: includes photostat and translations of a letter Kang Youwei sent to President Theodore Roosevelt, July 8, 1919; also includes related correspondence and other miscellaneous notes and ephemera., circa 1919-1937 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - William F. Hummel, China Society of Southern California, circa 1935-1975 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - William F. Hummel, China Society of Southern California, bulletins, 1939-1956 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - William F. Hummel, Chinese friends in California (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - William F. Hummel, Chinese friends in California (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - William F. Hummel, Chinese friends in California (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - William F. Hummel, notes and quotes (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - William F. Hummel, notes and quotes (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - William F. Hummel, notes and quotes (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - William F. Hummel, prayers and devotionals, circa 1973-1976 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - William F. Hummel, prayers and devotionals, circa 1973-1976 (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - William F. Hummel, prayers and devotionals, circa 1973-1976 (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - William F. Hummel, prayers and devotionals, circa 1973-1976 (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - William F. Hummel, Kingsley Manor, circa 1970-1976 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - William F. Hummel, Kingsley Manor, circa 1970-1976 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - William F. Hummel, Kingsley Manor, Sunday school lessons, circa 1970-1975 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - William F. Hummel, Kingsley Manor, Sunday school lessons, circa 1970-1975 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - William F. Hummel, Kingsley Manor, Sunday school lessons, circa 1970-1975 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - William F. Hummel, Kingsley Manor, Sunday school lessons, circa 1970-1975 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - William F. Hummel, Kingsley Manor, Sunday school lessons, circa 1970-1975 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - William F. Hummel, Kingsley Manor, Sunday school lessons, circa 1970-1975 (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - William F. Hummel, expense records, 1960 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - William F. Hummel, expense records, 1960 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - William F. Hummel, expense records, 1972 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - William F. Hummel, expense records, 1973 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - William F. Hummel, expense records, 1974 (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - William F. Hummel, expense records, 1975 (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - William F. Hummel, estate management and end-of-life documents, circa 1976 (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - William F. Hummel, estate management and end-of-life documents, circa 1976 (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - William F. Hummel, estate management and end-of-life documents, circa 1976 (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - William F. Hummel, estate management and end-of-life documents, circa 1976 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - William F. Hummel, estate management and end-of-life documents, circa 1976 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - William F. Hummel, estate management and end-of-life documents, circa 1976 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - William F. Hummel, estate management and end-of-life documents, circa 1976 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - William F. Hummel, biographical materials (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - William F. Hummel, biographical materials (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - William F. Hummel, biographical materials (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - William F. Hummel, biographical materials (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - William F. Hummel, biographical materials (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - William F. Hummel, biographical materials (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - William F. Hummel, biographical materials (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - William F. Hummel, biographical materials (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - William F. Hummel, biographical materials (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Subseries IV. WILLIAM F. HUMMEL CORRESPONDENCE, circa 1900-1975
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., 1913-1914 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., 1956-1966 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., June-September 1967 (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., October-December 1967 (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., January-June 1968 (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., July-December 1968 (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., January-March 1969 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., April-June 1969 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., July-September 1969 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., October-December 1969 (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., January-March 1970 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., April-June 1970 (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., July-September 1970 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., October-December 1970 (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., January-February 1971 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., March-April 1971 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., May-June 1971 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., July-September 1971 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., October-December 1971 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., January-February 1972 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., March-May 1972 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., June-August 1972 (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., September-December 1972 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., January-April 1973 (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., May-August 1973 (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., September-December 1973 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., January-May 1974 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., June-September 1974 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - William F. Hummel to Arthur W. Hummel Sr., October 1974-February 1975 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - William F. Hummel to relatives, 1910-1927 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - William F. Hummel to relatives, 1931-1976 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - William F. Hummel, letters and greeting cards in Chinese (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - William F. Hummel, miscellaneous incoming correspondence, circa 1930-1975 (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - William F. Hummel, miscellaneous incoming correspondence, circa 1930-1975 (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - William F. Hummel, miscellaneous incoming correspondence, circa 1930-1975 (Box 144, Folder 10)
  - Subseries V. MILDRED STUART HUMMEL and WILLIAM F. HUMMEL SHARED PERSONAL MATERIALS and SUBJECT FILES, circa 1907-1962
    - Summer resort, Kuling, China, circa 1907-1926 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Summer resort, Kuling, China, circa 1907-1926 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Hummel family, early years in China, circa 1908-1920 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Hummel family, early years in China, circa 1908-1920 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Mildred Stuart and William F. Hummel, marriage, circa October 1912 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Mildred Stuart and William F. Hummel, marriage, circa October 1912 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Mildred Stuart and William F. Hummel, marriage, circa October 1912 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Mildred Stuart and William F. Hummel, The Home Beautiful or the Wedded Life, wedding register, October 26, 1912 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Hummel family health in China, circa 1914-1921 (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Shansi, China, circa 1918-1920 (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Nanking Incident, circa 1927 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Nanking Incident, circa 1927 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Nanking Incident, circa 1927 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Nanking Incident, circa 1927 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Nanking Incident, circa 1927 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Nanking Incident, circa 1927 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Nanking Incident, circa 1927 (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - List of possessions looted from Hummel home in Nanking, circa 1927 (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - National Geographic Magazine, June 1967 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Peking postcard collection, circa 1933 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Chinese art collection, exhibit labels (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - US cross-country road trip, 1948 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - US cross-country road trip, botany, 1948 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - US cross-country road trip, 1954 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - US cross-country road trips, postcards, circa 1948-1954 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - US cross-country road trips, postcards, circa 1948-1954 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - US cross-country road trips, postcards, circa 1948-1954 (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - US cross-country road trips, postcards, circa 1948-1954 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - US cross-country road trips, postcards, circa 1948-1954 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - US cross-country road trips, brochures, circa 1948-1954 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - US cross-country road trips, brochures, circa 1948-1954 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - US cross-country road trips, brochures, circa 1948-1954 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Mildred Stuart and William F. Hummel, 50th wedding anniversary, 1962 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Mildred Stuart and William F. Hummel, 50th wedding anniversary, 1962 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Mildred Stuart and William F. Hummel, 50th wedding anniversary, 1962 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Mildred Stuart and William F. Hummel, 50th wedding anniversary, 1962 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Mildred Stuart and William F. Hummel, 50th wedding anniversary, 1962 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Mildred Stuart and William F. Hummel, 50th wedding anniversary, 1962 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Mildred Stuart and William F. Hummel, 50th wedding anniversary, 1962 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Mildred Stuart and William F. Hummel, 50th wedding anniversary, 1962 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Mildred Stuart and William F. Hummel, 50th wedding anniversary, 1962 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Mildred Stuart and William F. Hummel, 50th wedding anniversary, 1962 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Mildred Stuart and William F. Hummel, 50th wedding anniversary, 1962 (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Union Pacific Railway trip, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Union Pacific Railway trip, 1963 (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - Subseries VI. MILDRED STUART HUMMEL and WILLIAM F. HUMMEL CORRESPONDENCE, circa 1900-1975
    - Mildred Stuart Hummel to William F. Hummel, circa 1909-1911 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Mildred Stuart Hummel to William F. Hummel, circa 1909-1911 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Mildred Stuart Hummel to William F. Hummel, circa 1909-1911 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Mildred Stuart Hummel to William F. Hummel, circa 1909-1911 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Mildred Stuart Hummel to William F. Hummel, January-April 1911 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Mildred Stuart Hummel to William F. Hummel, May-June 1911 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Mildred Stuart Hummel to William F. Hummel, July-December 1911 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Mildred Stuart Hummel to William F. Hummel, January-May 1912 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Mildred Stuart Hummel to William F. Hummel, June-October 1912 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Mildred Stuart Hummel to William F. Hummel, 1916 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - William F. Hummel to Mildred Stuart Hummel, circa 1909-1911 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - William F. Hummel to Mildred Stuart Hummel, circa 1909-1911 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - William F. Hummel to Mildred Stuart Hummel, circa 1909-1911 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - William F. Hummel to Mildred Stuart Hummel, January-February 1911 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - William F. Hummel to Mildred Stuart Hummel, March-April 1911 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - William F. Hummel to Mildred Stuart Hummel, May-June 1911 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - William F. Hummel to Mildred Stuart Hummel, July-December 1911 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - William F. Hummel to Mildred Stuart Hummel, January-April 1912 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - William F. Hummel to Mildred Stuart Hummel, May-July 1912 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - William F. Hummel to Mildred Stuart Hummel, August-December 1912 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - William F. Hummel to Mildred Stuart Hummel, circa 1913-1917 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - William F. Hummel to Mildred Stuart Hummel, circa 1952-1965 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - William and Mildred Hummel, correspondence with Martha Solter, miscellaneous (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - William and Mildred Hummel, correspondence with Martha Solter, 1927-1931 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - William and Mildred Hummel, correspondence with Martha Solter, 1937-1955 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Hung Chen-Tao to William F. Hummel and Mildred Stuart Hummel, others, 1928 (Box 242, Folder 2)
    - Julie Thomson to William and Mildred Hummel, circa 1966-1969 (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - June Hummel Thomson to William and Mildred Hummel, circa 1967-1969 (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Ruth Isabelle Hummel Himmel to William and Mildred Hummel, circa 1967-1968 (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Ruth Isabelle Hummel Himmel and her children to William and Mildred Hummel, 1947-1976 (Box 152A, Volume 1)
    - Anne Stuart H. Kessler to William and Mildred Hummel, 1950-1975 (Box 153, Volume 1)
    - Outgoing Christmas cards, circa 1935-1969 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Greeting cards from Laurel and Fred Hummel, circa 1965-1967 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Incoming greeting cards, circa 1960-1975 (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Incoming greeting cards, circa 1960-1975 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Incoming greeting cards, circa 1960-1975 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Incoming greeting cards, circa 1960-1975 (Box 154, Folder 6)
- Series III. ARTHUR W. HUMMEL SR. FAMILY PAPERS, 1900-2001
  This series contains materials relating to Arthur W. Hummel Sr. and his immediate family. It has been divided into five subseries:
  Subseries I. Arthur W. Hummel Sr. Diaries and Subject files: photocopies of Arthur W. Hummel Sr.'s diaries and notebooks, mostly containing quotes and thoughts related to his travels in Asia and his personal and professional philosophy. There are also notes for lectures, translations of Chinese proverbs, and published and unpublished writings in the area of East Asian studies, including correspondence and notes regarding the publication of the Harriet Low diaries; materials related to his work at the Library of Congress, such as acquisition lists and bibliographies; also biographical materials, mostly photocopied letters and clippings highlighting major events in his personal and professional life.
  Note: Post 1950 notebooks are numbered from 1-20. R. Stuart Hummel indicated that notebooks 16, 17, and 19 are missing.
  Subseries II. Arthur W. Hummel Sr. Correspondence: mostly letters to his brother William F. Hummel, dating from 1927-1974; R. Stuart Hummel indicated letters from October 1970-April 1971 are missing, as are letters from November 1972-1973.
  Subseries III. Ruth Bookwalter Hummel: outgoing letters from Arthur Sr.'s wife Ruth to Mildred Stuart Hummel; also biographical materials. Subseries IV. Arthur W. Hummel Jr.: letters sent by Arthur Sr.'s son Arthur Jr. and his wife Betty Lou to R. Stuart and family, including a number letters sent while Arthur Jr. held diplomatic positions in Burma and China, detailing some of their activities and experiences in the 1980s. The remainder of the series contains interviews and miscellaneous biographical materials, consisting of clippings and photocopied letters highlighting Arthur Jr.'s career. Subseries V. Sharman B. Hummel and Carol Hummel Ames: biographical materials relating to Arthur Sr.'s son Sharman, daughter Carol, and their families.
  The following material is available online:
  The majority of original pre-1950 material in Series III, including correspondence and diaries
  Selected ephemera and subject files with original material from the period and selections of Arthur W. Hummel’s unpublished writings and materials relating to his work at the Library of Congress
  Letters from Arthur W. Hummel to William F. Hummel through 1975 (the correspondence focuses on their respective work and research and holds no significant third-party privacy concerns)
  Letters form Arthur W. Hummel Jr. and Betty Lou Hummel to R. Stuart through 2000 (his material mostly consists of letters reporting on Arthur Jr.’s career and holds no significant third-party privacy concerns).
  - Subseries I. ARTHUR W. HUMMEL SR. DIARIES and SUBJECT FILES
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., diaries, miscellaneous materials, 1901-1904 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., diaries, 1901-1904 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., Harriet Low diaries: correspondence, notes, and miscellaneous materials related to the publication of the Harriet Low diaries (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., Harriet Low diaries: correspondence, notes, and miscellaneous materials related to the publication of the Harriet Low diaries (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., notebooks, Japan, 1912-1914 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., notebooks, Fenchow, China, 1914-1924 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., notebooks, book 1, circa 1950 (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., notebooks, book 2, circa 1951-1954 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., notebooks, book 3, circa 1954-1955 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., notebooks, book 4, circa 1955 (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., notebooks, book 5, circa 1955 (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., notebooks, book 6, circa 1956 (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., notebooks, book 7, circa 1956 (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., notebooks, book 8, circa 1957 (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., notebooks, book 9, circa 1958 (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., notebooks, book 10, circa 1959 (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., notebooks, book 11, circa 1960-1975 (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., notebooks, book 12, circa 1960-1975 (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., notebooks, book 13, circa 1960-1975 (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., notebooks, book 14, circa 1960-1975 (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., notebooks, book 15, circa 1960-1975 (Box 156, Folder 17)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., notebooks, book 18, circa 1960-1975 (Box 156, Folder 18)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., notebooks, book 20, circa 1960-1975 (Box 156, Folder 19)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., Chinese and miscellaneous study notebooks (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., lecture notes (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., lecture notes (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., lecture notes (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., lecture notes (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., lecture notes (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., Chinese proverb translations (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., unpublished writings, miscellaneous (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., unpublished writings, early essays (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., unpublished writings, "The Far East in New Perspective", 1953 (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., unpublished writings, "The Understanding of Other Cultures: China", 1954 (Box 157, Folder 11)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., unpublished writings, "The Old Silk Road", 1968 (Box 157, Folder 12)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., unpublished writings, "Taoism", 1973 (Box 157, Folder 13)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., unpublished writings, "Notes on Chinese Painting" (Box 157, Folder 14)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., unpublished writings, "Glimpses of Indian Wisdom" (Box 157, Folder 15)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., unpublished writings, "Hu Wei" (Box 157, Folder 16)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., unpublished writings, "The Chinese View of Life" (Box 157, Folder 17)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., unpublished writings, "The Humanities: East and West" (Box 157, Folder 18)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., unpublished writings, "A Sixteenth Century Exile" (Box 157, Folder 19)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., bibliography of published writings, 1915-1964 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., published writings (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., published writings (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., published writings (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., published writings (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Arthur W. Hummel Sr., published writings (Box 158, Folder 6)